{
  "results": [
    {
      "question": "What was the first food spot we ate together alone?",
      "correct_answer": "Myungrang",
      "answerList": ["Myungrang", "Tsujita", "The Taco Stand", "My Pho"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What was the first movie we watched together?",
      "correct_answer": "Searching",
      "answerList": ["Searching", "Princess Mononoke", "Nacho Libre", "Mad Max"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What's the name of the comedy venue we visited on our second date?",
      "correct_answer": "The Comedy Store",
      "answerList": [
        "The Comedy Store",
        "Laugh Factory",
        "Hollywood Improv",
        "Upright Citizens Brigade Theatre"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Finish this lyrical line. \"When I can't go to sleep unless you're...\"",
      "correct_answer": "laying next to me",
      "answerList": [
        "laying next to me",
        "within my arms",
        "holding on to me",
        "safe and sound"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What's the dog's name in Overcooked 2?",
      "correct_answer": "Kevin",
      "answerList": ["Kevin", "Max", "Johnny", "Chris"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What's the order of the elements in the intro of Avatar: The Last Airbender?",
      "correct_answer": "Water, Earth, Fire, Air",
      "answerList": [
        "Water, Earth, Fire, Air",
        "Earth, Air, Water, Fire",
        "Water, Fire, Air, Earth",
        "Air, Fire, Water, Earth"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What's the name of Randy's childhood Chinese restaurant we visited in San Diego?",
      "correct_answer": "Royal Mandarin",
      "answerList": [
        "Royal Mandarin",
        "Panda Palace",
        "Mandarin Wok",
        "Emerald Chinese"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is NOT an ice cream flavor from The Bodega Capsule?",
      "correct_answer": "Budget Brunch",
      "answerList": [
        "Budget Brunch",
        "Chico Stix",
        "Host of Cupcakes",
        "Bodega Counter Crunch"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What was the date when we first met?",
      "correct_answer": "August 17",
      "answerList": ["August 17", "August 15", "August 16", "August 18"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is NOT one of the sites we visited at Sequoia National Park?",
      "correct_answer": "Grant Grove",
      "answerList": [
        "Grant Grove",
        "Moro Rock",
        "General Sherman Tree",
        "Crescent Meadow"
      ]
    }
  ]
}
